My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom
and saving the multiverse,
I ran back in time and created
the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
What is that?
Another epidermal husk,
a fully-intact human pelt.
Do we have any theories
as to what's causing them?
- I am Alchemy.
- Well, what do you want?
To help people achieve their true potential.
I know you want this more than anything,
but you have to face the fact
that it might not happen.
There's a whole multiverse
of Harrison Wells out there.
- Call me HR.
- You're a fake.
Let me prove my worth.
If I fail, I will right back to my Earth.
If I succeed, I will have
done some good with my life.
Caitlin, these powers you have,
the more you use them,
the more difficult
they're going to be to reverse.
I'm fast,
really fast.
I might even be the fastest man alive.
And when I'm running,
there's no greater feeling in the world.
I can move through the city
like a guardian angel,
protecting people who need me.
Whoa, you gotta slow down.
And watch where you're going, okay?
- Okay.
Cool skateboard, though.
Thanks.
They even have a name for me.
They call me "Kid Flash."
Kid Flash?
Yeah, the name needs some work, but, Dad,
I'm telling you, it all just felt so real
like it was actually happening.
And how often are you getting these dreams?
Uh, last couple nights.
Last couple?
Wally, this is exactly
what Frankie Kane said happened to her.
She had dreams, a lot of painful ones,
and then she started hearing
Alchemy's voice in her head
- until she became Magenta.
- Yeah.
This is totally different, Dad.
No. No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
I'm a speedster in my dreams.
I'm not an evil split personality.
I'm helping people, not hurting them.
Dad, this could mean that
my powers are finally manifesting.
No, I think this means
that you have a lot in common
right now with people who either
ended up in prison or dead.
Except for the fact that
I got hit by the dark matter
from the particle accelerator explosion,
just like Jesse.
I'm going to class.
Hey, Julian, do you want me to get started
on the DNA analysis for you?
Why would I need you to do that?
I don't know, I just
figured we worked so well
together last time.
What, that I'd want to do it again?
One shared case and one shared drink
does not make us mates, okay?
Miss Horton.
Mr. Allen.
- Mr. Albert.
- Morning.
New one?
Uh, yeah, number six.
Found it last night.
Well, this should
come as a welcome surprise.
You've been reassigned to meta-human
crime scene investigation full-time.
Full-time?
We're pouring all the resources we can
into figuring out this
husk problem, especially
considering the last one turned out to be
that evil speedster, The Rival.
Any questions, concerns,
you guys direct them
to Judge Hankerson, yeah?
All right. Thank you.
Joe.
- Cecile.
- Hi.
I didn't know you were gonna be over here.
Any excuse I have
to run into you, I take it.
You know, I'm really looking
forward to tomorrow night.
So am I.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay, good, then I, uh,
- I'll see you then.
- All right.
Yo. Is that what I think it was?
You asked her to movie night with us?
That's awesome. When did you do that?
How'd you do it?
As much as I'd like to gossip with you
like a teenager right now,
there's something else
we need to talk about.
What?
Wally.
He's been having dreams.
Dreams?
Saving people,
becoming a speedster.
He called himself Kid Flash.
Kid Flash, he...
he said that name, specifically?
He's in trouble, isn't he?
If Wally's having dreams of being Kid Flash,
then he's in trouble,
yeah, but don't worry,
okay, we'll figure it out.
- I'll see you later.
- All right.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
We have a problem.
Yeah, we do. He's still here.
Cisco, comedy of the obvious.
I made a pact to justify
my presence on your Earth
and I think I got something.
- We're all ears.
- Okay.
I read every news report
I can get my hands on.
And I have come to the conclusion
that this very operation
is a ticking time-bomb.
What do you mean?
You can't spend all your time working on...
working on whatever... whatever this is.
This... this is a very delicate
set of power-dampening cuffs.
We need them to stop the meta-humans.
My point exactly.
It's not gonna be long
before people start
putting the pieces together
and figure out what you're doing here.
You're working with The Flash.
Okay, so what's your idea?
The perfect disguise.
We reopen this laboratory
and I become the face of
the new S.T.A.R. Labs
Museum.
There's only one problem with that.
It's your face.
You're kind of a known murderer
around these parts.
You see, the evil Wells,
not to be confused with
the dick-ish but not evil Wells,
he confessed to killing Barry's mother.
So basically, if you step foot
outside this lab, you'll be arrested.
What... you're just telling me
this now, you two rascals?
What about the cryptogram?
What about the message?
Come to this Earth. Get a fresh start.
Well, what about your résumé
as a world-renowned genius scientist?
That's a good point. I guess we're even.
If a string is in a knot,
patience will untie it.
Patience can do lots of things.
Have you ever tried it?
My dear ma used to say that
to me all the time
any time I had a problem.
Now I have a problem.
I guess I'm gonna use that adage
to figure it out.
S.T.A.R. Labs Museum, think about it.
You think everyone on Earth-19
is missing crayons in the box,
or just him?
Paging Dr. Snow.
Wow, you are out of it. Sorry.
This have anything to do
with your recent visit with mom?
I just... I haven't been sleeping well,
but I'm okay.
Coffee?
Perfect.
So I did have powers?
I was Kid Flash?
In Flashpoint, yes.
I knew that this was happening.
Why didn't you tell me before?
Because...
Because why?
All right, fine, Wally, it, look...
in that timeline,
you were fighting The Rival.
Edward Clariss?
Edward Clariss, yeah.
You couldn't stop him.
There was no S.T.A.R. Labs.
There was no team to help you.
It was just you and Iris.
The two of you were a brother-sister
superhero crime-fighting team.
Why didn't you tell us this before?
You didn't want to know
about your Flashpoint lives.
But look, listen to me,
you got hurt, all right?
You got hurt bad.
So what?
That's that me, it's not this me.
And I want to be a speedster.
I... I want to be a flash.
No, no, no, you don't.
Yes, I do.
You're not hearing what he's saying.
He's telling us it's not safe.
Who cares what Barry's saying?
How do we even know he's telling the truth?
Wally, come on, this isn't because of
the particle accelerator,
it's because of Dr. Alchemy.
It's the same thing
that happened to Frankie Kane.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, we do.
And we need to try
to keep it from happening.
Why don't we just say
what this is really about?
You're okay with Barry having powers;
you're okay with Barry running into danger,
fighting all these metas.
He can screw up over and over again
You're okay with all of it
because he's Barry.
But you won't give me
the same amount of leeway
because at the end of the day,
you just don't trust me.
You know that's not true, Wally.
I don't need you fighting
my dad's battles for him.
Say it, Joe.
You don't trust me, do you?
Wally...
That's what I thought.
Hey, hey...
No. No, you're not listening to me.
I said the shares are undervalued
so if the stock drops,
you should buy more, not less.
No, that... that's not how it works.
Look, just look at its balance sheet.
If you sell now, you're going
to lose a lot of money.
I understand that.
Of course it's your money.
Just hold onto it then.
You know what? If you're not gonna listen...
Petechiae around the eye,
the crushed larynx.
This poor chap has got
fingerprints all round his neck.
He's clearly been strangled.
I heard multiple witnesses
said the man was attacked by a shadow.
Huh.
So a meta from Neverland's made the trip
to Central City Fabulous.
So far there's no forensic evidence
that there was an assailant.
No laceration marks. No fingernail marks.
No DNA evidence underneath
the fingernails even?
Nothing yet, we'll have to wait and see.
There's always something.
Bag the body up and
I'll meet you back at the lab.
- Yeah.
- See ya.
Oh, and Julian, um,
I'm going to that movie in the park thing
with Joe and his... or my...
Iris and some other friends.
Uh, if you felt like going,
it starts at 8:00.
We're all a bunch of nerds, so
you'll fit right in.
Well, that's a very enticing offer, Allen,
but I'm actually seeing
my girlfriend tonight, so.
Oh, you have a girlfriend?
I didn't know that.
I'm sure there's lots
about me that you don't know.
- Cheerio.
- Yeah.
- Albert.
- Detective.
- Hey.
- Anything?
With the... uh, nothing yet, at least.
Have you seen Wally this morning?
No. Why?
He left the house in a huff.
He won't answer my calls.
Iris is out there looking for him right now.
Did you want me to run around the city?
Maybe if I can't get ahold of him.
What Wally said, it's partially true.
I didn't answer his question because
I... I don't trust him with these powers
the same way I trust you with them.
You got to talk to him about that.
You know, tell him why, especially now.
I will, I mean, just gotta find him first.
Look, I'll just keep calling him.
He's got to answer at some point, right?
Man, I feel bad, too.
It's your first date with Cecile
and you got to worry about this.
Don't worry about that.
That's one part of my life I can control.
Yes?
Have you seen HR?
Maybe he's meditating in his room.
No, he's not there.
HR, you're needed in the Speed Lab, now.
He could be doing inversion
stretches in the intake.
You saw that too, huh?
HR! He's not there.
Probably just brewing another pot of coffee.
- It's all he drinks.
- Not that either.
Okay. Why do you need him so badly?
He's going through my stuff, but now...
He's just being stupid about it.
Stupid about what?
God, I swear I fixed the security system.
Who the hell are you?
HR.
Apologies.
See? Ah. What you've just been witness to
was my partner's likeness, Randolf Morgan.
Okay, I see what's going on here.
You don't have facial transmogrification
on this planet, do you?
No, we certainly do not.
Well then,
it's a good thing for me
I found this little contraption
in my satchel... forgot I brought it.
It's so fun.
So fun? How does this work?
Light refraction technology.
Light refraction?
I think... I don't... Randolf,
my... business partner,
he's sort of more with the science.
But this little sucker
is gonna go a long way
to solving my Harrison Wells facial issues.
I'm gonna hang onto this
until I get my power cuffs back.
What, your power cuffs?
Your meta-human power-dampening cuffs?
Those very ones, the ones that are
missing all of a sudden.
What... you think... you think I took them?
I didn't take them.
What do I need cuffs for?
I just got to this Earth. I came alone.
I haven't met anyone yet;
it's gonna take a while,
even when I do meet them,
to get to the cuff stage.
Hey, guys?
Guys, I need you in the Cortex.
Killed by a shadow? That's a new one.
Maybe that's what killed Edward Clariss.
Clariss was a meta-human.
This victim doesn't appear to be.
Do we know if this shadow meta is from the
particle accelerator explosion
or from Dr. Alchemy?
Not yet, no.
We actually haven't found any
evidence to process.
If only we had a way, Francisco,
to see what happened.
Where was the crime scene located?
In Chubbuck, uh, Palmer and Racine,
around 11:00 last night.
- Whoa.
That's gonna give me night terrors.
- Shade.
- What?
We had a meta-hominid on my planet
who could do virtually the same thing,
called himself "Shade."
What did he do, throw
his side-eye at his enemies?
No, I know, it's a terrible nickname, right?
But what Shade could do was
vibrate at such a high frequency
he created the illusion
that he was a shadow.
That's how I phase.
Do you think he's doing the same thing?
He has to be.
Heat signature's fluctuating.
Red shift is ridiculous.
Okay, so he is.
He must be slowing down his
molecules whenever he attacks.
So we just have to figure out
a way to keep them slowed down,
and that should be enough to grab him.
All right, can you get started?
Okay, but, like, right this minute?
Yeah, I'm sor... we just...
we gotta stop this guy fast
so we can focus on Alchemy.
Wally has been having
dreams about being a speedster,
Alchemy dreams.
He was a speedster in Flashpoint?
Anyone else gonna have powers
we should know about?
No.
All right. I'm gonna work on Shade.
- I'll supervise.
- You're gonna find my cuffs.
I'll have to find some cuffs.
All right, I got to get back to work
before Julian loses his mind.
Wally, it's your dad, again.
Just give me a call back, all right?
Or a text, I just need to know you're okay.
I'm okay.
Wally.
You can't do that.
You can't just disappear.
I just wanted to let you know
I'm fine, so.
Come here.
Listen, you were right.
I do treat Barry differently
than I treat you.
But not because I think
Barry's better than you.
Then why?
Wally, you're a lot like I was as a kid.
You're fearless and you take risks
and that makes you
a handful just like I was.
And now you're getting powers.
That alone would make me nervous
because I know what I
would have done if I got powers.
But you're not getting your speed
the same way Barry got his.
You're getting your speed the way
Magenta and The Rival got theirs.
So it's not that I don't
trust you, Wally, it's just
I don't trust what's
going on with you right now.
And that scares the living hell out of me.
I know, Dad.
I get it.
Okay, so
let's get you to S.T.A.R. Labs
- and see what we can do.
- All right.
Wallace.
Wallace West.
Ah!
Wally.
Wally!
Hey, Cisco.
Yes?
I took your cuffs.
Why?
Because I need them.
Is... is this some sort of, um,
bold fashion choice 'cause
you're not a meta-hu... hu...
human.
Surprise.
It started a few months ago.
That's why you went to see your mom,
to see if she could help you.
But she can't.
I've run every test.
There's nothing that anyone can do.
I need a favor.
I need you to vibe me in the future
because I need to know if I become...
her.
You're not gonna become her.
Okay, just because you have these powers
doesn't mean you're gonna
turn into Killer Frost.
I think it might.
Please?
I just need to know for sure.
I need to know if I become evil
because if I do, I have to leave
and never come back.
And?
I didn't see anything.
You're fine.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Please, um,
don't tell anyone about this yet, okay?
- Of course.
- Okay.
According to this,
all your vitals are fine, Wally.
Wally, what did you see?
I was Kid Flash again, but
this time it wasn't a good dream.
I was fighting The Rival
at some abandoned sawmill.
That's what happened in Flashpoint
before you got hurt.
They're not just dreams,
they must be memories of that life.
More and more people are getting powers.
Okay, so how do we stop this?
I mean, is there any stopping it even?
If Alchemy could reach you at CCPD,
he could probably reach you
from anywhere, right?
I have a suggestion.
Why don't we throw Wallace in the pipeline
until we figure this situation out.
You want to lock him up?
Yeah, I agree with Joe, we lock him up
because think about this.
We can't stop Alchemy from
getting into Wallace's head,
but we put him in the pipeline,
then we control the situation
from there on out.
As much as I don't like it, Dad,
maybe he's not wrong.
But only till we figure out
a better way to make you safe.
Yeah, I agree with Joe.
I'm gonna cancel this movie with Cecile.
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa, wait, wait,
you've got a date with Cecile?
Yeah, I was gonna bring her
to movie in the park tonight.
Well, don't not go.
You've put your life on hold
for us long enough.
Yeah, Dad, he's right, I mean,
go be Joe West; you're always Dad.
Yeah, we'll stay with Wally,
and make sure nothing happens.
I told her all of you were coming with me.
Am I gonna be the only one that shows up?
Uh, I would love to see a movie.
- What movie is this?
- "The Shining."
"The Shining," oh, I love that movie.
That movie freaks you out.
You have never made it past
the part with the Grady twins.
That's... that's... that was...
I was younger.
Why don't I go with you?
You sure you don't want stay...
No, I want to be with you.
Either way, the more the merrier.
Let's do it.
Hell, this will be
great fodder for my novel.
Hold on, you guys didn't tell him about?
Joe, no.
They... they told me,
finally, the little scamps.
But I think that I've worked my way
around that little problem.
Watch this.
Whoa.
Oh, um, let me just...
- What... ah...
- What did you do?
Did you just neuralyze us?
No, I gave you a simple retinal adjustment
so all of you can see me, HR,
while the rest of the world sees...
Randolf Morgan.
Joe, I promise,
I'll be so... I'll be so quiet.
You won't even know I'm there.
Silent observer.
All right.
Wally, keep me posted.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Just go have fun.
That's great.
All right, we want to be 2/3 to the back,
- right in the middle.
- That's a very small screen.
Like, I don't know if we're
gonna be able to see from...
No, HR, the screen is perfect, okay?
- We'll be able to see fine.
- But we're so far...
That's where the engineer sits when
- he mixes the sound, all right?
- All right.
When you want to get the
Kubrick experience, that's...
- All right, yeah.
- The sweet spot, right there.
I don't know, maybe we get a
little closer, like right by...
Why don't you let us worry about the seats?
You take care of the snacks and the drinks.
Great idea.
Any time.
Oh, I don't...
I'm pretty sure they're
not gonna take the money from my Earth.
- I don't think.
- What?
- What is this?
- That's a helbing.
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna get us what we need,
you're gonna do that, go over
to that stand over there.
- Great idea.
- You're gonna get us some
- licorice sticks, some Jujubes.
- Licorice... Juju...
Yeah, and coffee.
Do you want anything?
- No thanks.
- Okay.
Okay.
You okay, Cisco?
Yeah. Yeah, you know,
just trying to deal with HR.
Yeah, 'cause you've been on edge
ever since you vibed me.
Are you gonna tell me what you saw?
Yeah, I told you what I saw.
No, but, for real.
I can tell when you're
not being honest with me.
Am I her?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're her.
I... I saw the both of us
fighting.
Like, full-on Vibe versus Killer Frost.
It's like we're meta-frenemies.
Well, have you ever vibed
anything from the future
that didn't come true?
Just Earth-2 being ripped to shreds.
But that doesn't mean
that can't happen again.
Caitlin,
you have to tell them.
You have to tell the team.
We have to figure out what's going on.
No. It's too late.
There's nothing you can do.
Nobody else needs to know.
I haven't been to a movie in forever.
I come whenever I can, I mean,
sort of a summer tradition with the kids.
Yeah?
You know, it's funny,
you don't really peg me
for a, uh, horror movie type.
I thought maybe you'd be
more of a chick-flicky.
- Oh, you got jokes.
- Yeah.
I might be mad if you weren't so gorgeous.
Gorgeous, really?
If I'm so gorgeous, then how come you're
spending more time looking
at that than you are at me?
You know what?
You're right, Cecile, I'm sorry.
My son, Wally,
he's...
going through some changes and I'm just...
- Hey.
- Just really concerned.
Joe, we can do this another time.
No-no-no-no, I really
want to be here with you, I do.
It's just that when
one of my kids is hurting I'm...
Can't think about anything else at all.
Completely understand.
- You have kids?
- Yeah.
- Daughter.
- Oh.
Just turned 18.
I have less than a year before
she leaves me for college.
Oh, man, you should have brought her.
I drag you away from her
so you can watch a horror movie.
Not many men could.
I'm just glad you finally
figured out what you want.
Me too.
Wally, you okay?
- I hate that we have to do this.
- Mm.
He so badly wanted powers,
and, now, to keep him locked up
so he doesn't get them, it's...
It's hard, I know.
I don't know if you actually do.
What does that mean?
All Wally wants to do is to help people.
And to see you do that every day
while all he can do
is stand by and watch,
it's hard being a bystander sometimes.
You don't feel that way too, do you?
Barry...
Come on.
My contributions here are limited.
I don't know science.
I don't have powers.
I don't know how to help you.
I couldn't do this without you.
That's not true.
That is true.
Whether you realize it or not,
there is no Flash
without Iris West.
I'm wolfing this.
- I'm telling you, it's so good.
- It is good.
What is it about popcorn and the movies?
Hey, you okay?
- Hey.
- Yeah, fine.
- Hi, I'm Caitlin.
- Hi.
Cecile. Nice to meet you.
And you must be Cisco. That's me.
Nice to meet you. Hi.
Don't forget about me.
Hello.
I'm HR.
HR Randolf.
It's amazing to meet you.
- All right, now.
- Amazing.
And so then... then she says to me,
"Oh, so you are hot chocolate
from another land."
I said, "Okay, easy, now."
Then she, "Wait a minute.
Do you speak a foreign language?"
What did you say?
Well, I said, "Sure."
"As long as I know the words."
I'm gonna smack somebody.
Everybody, move, move!
It's Shade.
He's at Hofherr Park.
Wallace.
Wallace West.
The time has come
to restore what was taken from you.
to set you free.
Hey, hey, the same thing
happened to Frankie.
You have to fight through the pain.
Are you okay?
I think so.
Find me.
And I will release you from all of this.
Wally, what is it?
You have to open the door.
I... I can't do that, Wally. I can't.
I can make you whole again.
Open the door! I need to get out!
Now!
Flash, just who I came to see.
So you like shadows?
Want to try and catch mine?
Barry, we're in the van. Can you hear us?
And I just got tossed
on my ass like a rag doll.
That's not good.
All right, guys,
I cannot do anything if I can't see him.
Can we light this place up?
Light's gonna slow down
his molecular vibration
so we can catch him.
How are we gonna light this place up?
- See all these cars?
- Yeah.
- I hack into their computers.
- Yeah?
- The park's overhead lights.
Blast this guy with more lumens
- than a Pink Floyd concert.
- Yeah.
What are you doing?
He's gonna need these.
- She took...
- She took the cuffs.
Okay, just drop it, all right?
Barry, I'm in.
Okay.
All right, wait until my mark.
And by mark,
I do mean
next time that I get punched.
Mark.
Flash!
Don't like the light, do you?
Nowhere to hide now.
Get me out. Get me out... ah!
Help me!
Please, make it stop.
Ah, Iris!
Hey, Wally, Wally, Wally, look.
It's over, okay? Come on, come on...
Find me.
Stay out of my way.
Wally, stop.
Stay out of my way!
Wally wasn't himself.
He was possessed.
Alchemy was calling for him.
I knew I shouldn't have left.
It's okay, Joe, nothing happened.
He's not okay, Barry.
This thing's coming after him, and...
and there ain't a damn thing we can do?
Well, we stopped Shade.
And now we can focus on Alchemy, all right?
Unless he sends another meta
to Central City to attack.
Then we're in trouble.
You think Shade was a distraction?
I agree with Iris;
I think the attack on Wally
and the attack by Shade happened
at essentially the same time.
So that's not a coincidence.
If that's true, that means
Alchemy's gonna sending
another one of his metas soon.
We don't know that.
Barry, we found six husks.
So besides Shade, Magenta, and Clariss,
there's still three unaccounted for.
Okay, well, if more come,
then we'll stop them.
But Alchemy can't get Wally
if he stays in the cell.
Barry, we can't just let
Wally suffer in there.
And besides, burying our head in the sand
is not gonna make Alchemy go away.
Ignoring the problem does not get rid of it.
You're gonna have to face it.
Don't we?
- What?
- Nothing.
Come on, Caitlin.
Not right now, Cisco.
I... just... I can't just keep this in.
You have to tell them.
Tell them what?
I have powers.
What?
What kind of powers?
The cold kind.
Happy now?
So, what, we're just gonna
keep secrets from each other?
Yeah, well, this wasn't your secret to tell,
was it, Cisco?
I did that because I care about you.
If you cared about me, then you would have
let me tell them all when I was ready.
Because this is happening to me, not you.
I'm the one turning evil.
I'm the one who's gonna have to leave soon.
I vibed the two of us fighting
each other in the future.
She was Killer Frost.
- I'll go talk to her.
- I got it.
How long have you known?
A few months.
First I didn't want to accept
what was happening to me.
And then I had to.
So then I tried to suppress my powers.
There's no suppressing these powers.
I just can't believe that this is my life.
It shouldn't be.
None of what's happening
to any of you should be.
What do you mean, any of us?
I mean...
Dr. Alchemy.
Wally.
You getting powers.
Even Dante being dead in this timeline.
It's all because I created Flashpoint.
Even Iris, who, I don't know, I think
she's disappointed that
she doesn't have powers
and everyone else does.
And no matter what I do now,
everything's different.
So none of this happened before?
I'm sorry, Caitlin.
Wally's up.
Okay.
How you feeling?
I've been better.
What do we do?
We got to come up with something.
Use me.
No. No, no, hell no.
Alchemy's calling for me to go to him.
Follow me wherever he is,
and we can stop him.
No. We're not asking you to do that.
This is our chance to stop him
We have to do it.
Wally...
Dad, he... he wants me.
He's hurting me.
So let me fight back.
Wally?
Find me.
Turn him on his side.
All right, get him over, come on.
This should help.
It's a mild sedative.
- What is that?
- Lorazepam.
It works on seizures.
Hopefully it'll work on whatever this is.
These episodes keep happening
more frequently.
Yeah, and this is just a temporary fix.
If we don't stop it too, he could suffer
from permanent brain damage.
We don't have a choice.
We have to do what Wally wanted; we have to
use him to find Alchemy.
No, we're no... it's too dangerous.
So is doing nothing.
Need I remind everyone that Dr. Alchemy
has a rock that shoots lasers, so who knows
what he has up his sleeve?
Cisco's right.
What if we're walking into a trap?
You guys aren't walking into anything.
You guys are gonna stay here.
If we're gonna do this,
we're gonna do it right.
What does that mean?
It means that if I'm
gonna put Wally at risk,
I'm gonna use everything
in my power to protect him.
Double-check your packs.
Make sure we have everything.
- Good to go.
- Okay.
So what's the plan, Detective?
This lunatic, calls himself Alchemy,
he's the one responsible for all these husks
we've been finding all over town.
But we believe we found a way
to get his location.
How?
By using his next target.
Your son?
We'll stop him, Joe.
Where's Julian?
He didn't come in today.
What, he never misses a day. You call him?
Yeah, it went straight to voicemail.
Well.
All right, gents, move out.
Let's roll.
All right, be safe.
We'll see you in a few.
You ready?
Yeah.
Hey, you remember when
I said that you remind me
of myself as a kid?
I was never this brave.
They've just left.
I'm almost done. I'll be right there.
Cisco, I am so sorry about how I reacted.
I understand why you told everyone.
Never helps when we
keep things from each other.
You're right.
And I'm glad that you told everyone.
I'm just not very good at asking for help.
I get that from my mom.
You're better than your mother.
I don't know.
I'm just so terrified because she said
if I keep using my powers, then
it'll be impossible to stop them.
Your mother might be
one of the most accomplished
scientists on this planet,
but when it comes to the impossible,
we're the experts.
We're gonna help you, Caitlin.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Let's go help Wally.
You got it.
We're moving in.
Just remember, once you get in there,
we're not gonna have eyes
Copy that.
Of course, dude uses an
abandoned subway to set up shop.
Of course he does.
Where's Grodd when you need him?
Gro... Gorilla Grodd?
You have sentient gorillas
on your Earth too?
Oh,
oh, yeah, yeah, we do, many.
Many. Yeah.
Come to me.
Wallace.
Everybody set?
We're good.
Just lead the way.
You okay?
Yeah.
It's okay to be scared, Wally.
I am.
You are?
Keeps me alert.
Then I'm on high alert.
Let's do this.
Hello, Wally.
Are you him?
Are you the voice I've been
hearing inside my head?
I am Alchemy.
I've been having visions
of another life.
Where... where I have speed, where, I'm...
The Flash.
I can give you that back,
should you desire it.
I just want the pain to stop.
It will, child.
Whatever you desire,
I will see it so.
Now tell me,
do you wish for the life
that was taken from you
to return?
What I wish for...
is all of you gone.
It's a trap!
No!
The boy has been chosen, Flash.
And you will not stand
before what must be...
Ever again!
No!
Get on your knees!
Now! Don't move!
Don't move! Get down!
On the ground.
I said get on the ground.
That was a grave mistake.
- You okay?
- I'll be fine.
Wally?
Yeah.
It's over, Alchemy.
Over?
You have no idea
what's about to begin.
What the hell?
Did you guys see that?
See what?
Go. Get the hell out of here!
Wally, move towards the door!
Stick with me!
The other way! The other way!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Wally, go!
You all right?
Wallace.
Wallace West.
Take your power.
Wally.
Wally, don't!
Wally!
Who are you?
Savitar.
The God of Speed.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com